lgnewsroom.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy | LG Newsroom

LG Electronics is committed to protecting your privacy on the Internet. We believe that it is important for you to know what we do with your personal information. When it comes to consumer data collected electronically, LG Electronics will provide notice, choice, access and security in ways described below. In general, you, as our customer, can visit LG Electronics on the World Wide Web without having to reveal any personal information that you do not want to disclose.

Our web servers collect domain names and not the e-mail addresses. This information may be aggregated on a “no names” basis just to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, or pages viewed. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a “cookie” (a small data file) on your computer’s hard drive which allows the server to recognize the computer when it visits again. This helps track statistical information about navigation through our site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation. LG Electronics uses these data to measure the usage of, and improve the content of our sites. In an effort to make your visit both efficient and safe, all transfers of personal information via this site meet LG Electronics’ rigorous Internet security standards.

Occasionally, our site may contain electronic links to other sites. In case you choose to go to those sites, their own privacy policy and privacy preferences will apply.

If you feel that the LG Electronics Web site (http://www.lgnewsroom.com) is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, contact the Webmaster or send your concerns to the LG Twin Towers, 20, Yeouido-dong, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea.
